Contact

angiedreiling2@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angelazimmerman-dreiling-042207104 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Education Clinical Skills Teaching

Languages

English

Certifications

BLS

ACLS

Angela Zimmerman Dreiling

IR Travel Nurse

Greater Salt Lake City Area

Summary

With 15+ years of experience in direct patient care, clinic management, and educator roles, I've become an exceptional leader who continuously seeks out opportunities to increase care outcomes. I've also acted as an educator who can design and deliver curriculum to all levels of students in preparation for testing and clinical practice. Please take a few moments to review my experience below and reach out if you have any questions.

Experience

RNnetwork
IR travel nurse
July 2019 - Present (1 year)

Paragon Healthcare, Inc. Infusion Nurse April 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Living Hope Home HealthCare Home Health Nurse RN March 2019 - June 2019 (4 months) PRN

The Courtyards at Pasadena Assistant Director Of Nursing October 2018 - February 2019 (5 months) Pasadena

Alate Health formerly Houston VIR RN/Clinical Manager 2016 - October 2018 (2 years) Houston, Texas

Bayshore 24hr Emergency Center

Page 1 of 3

Emergency Room RN 2014 - 2015 (1 year)

Pasadena, Texas

Duties included:

Proficiency with the Meditech system

Triaging, Assessing/Evaluation of patients, quick critical thinking skills, and working as a team to provide excellent patient care.

A&B Educational Services CEO/Owner 2010 - 2013 (3 years)

Creating nursing curriculum, tutoring/teaching nursing material, business development, marketing new students, and developing and maintaining positive relationships between students and coworkers.

Emergency Consultants Nursing Instructor 2007 - 2010 (3 years)

Tutoring/teaching given instructional nursing material, providing a positive classroom environment, maintaining good working relationships between students and coworkers.

Houston Metro Urology Nursing Liaison for Radiation Oncologist 2006 - 2007 (1 year)

Developing a new clinic, which involved: researching and ordering any and all clinic supplies, streamlining the process between patients and physician interaction, maintaining positive working relationships with other healthcare team members, and performing any and all nursing procedures required.

Education

Texas A&M University

Bachelor's degree, Community Health and Preventive Medicine · (1994 - 1997)

San Jacinto College Associates of Nursing

The University of Texas at Arlington Bachelors of Nursing · (2020 - 2020)